[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which bridge terms refer to two weak openings?", "correct_answer": "Multi and Muiderberg", "incorrect_answers": ["Jacoby and Leiden", "Stayman and Amsterdam", "Yarborough and Utrecht"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The line There is no Y in Egypt comes from which movie?", "correct_answer": "Five Graves to Cairo", "incorrect_answers": ["The Desert Fox", "Casablanca", "The Battle of El Alamein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these dishes is a traditional Mexican dish, prepared out of a tortilla dipped in a sauce, containing peppers?", "correct_answer": "Enchilada", "incorrect_answers": ["Polenta", "Baccala", "Jambalaya"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is common for adults to have to care for their children and  their parents. Parker Posey and Demi Moore star in this 2009 movie about one such situation.", "correct_answer": "Happy Tears", "incorrect_answers": ["From Zero to Sixty", "Face Value", "In Deep"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A character played by which actor said: While you were at court, I was in this damned dirty armor 20 years! Ive had nothing...NOTHING!!!?", "correct_answer": "Charlton Heston in The Warlord", "incorrect_answers": ["Lawrence Olivier in Spartacus", "Russell Crowe in Gladiator", "Richard Harris in Cromwell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What vegetable is the main ingredient of the popular Spanish soup called Gazpacho?", "correct_answer": "Tomato", "incorrect_answers": ["Red pepper", "Potato", "Carrot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Filipino word lungsod mean in English?", "correct_answer": "city", "incorrect_answers": ["market", "island", "province"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these substances and minerals is not effective in the treatment of depression?", "correct_answer": "Sodium", "incorrect_answers": ["Zinc", "Magnesium", "Dopamine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2000 this actor starred in the gruesome psychological thriller American Psycho.", "correct_answer": "Christian Bale", "incorrect_answers": ["Brad Pitt", "Tom Berringer", "Tom Hanks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Billy Jack in the popular series of movies?", "correct_answer": "Tom Laughlin", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Jones", "Tom Selleck", "Tom Cruise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Shakespeares last play?", "correct_answer": "The Tempest", "incorrect_answers": ["A Lovers Complaint", "Romeo and Juliet", "The Winters Tale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Found in tonic water, quinine is commonly used to treat malaria.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]